September 1st.
9月1日
The first day back after summer break
迎來新學期的這一天
is a depressing one for many students.
聽說這天會令許多學生 陷入憂鬱的心情
Be it despair over the end of summer, or unease about their environment,
有人感嘆夏天轉眼間就結束了 有人對新環境感到不安
the cause is not certain, but here's what Tadano thought…
雖然不確定本意 但只野同學是這麼認為的…
-OH MY GOSH, IT'S KOMI… -"The kids here seem just fine."
-是古見同學耶 -“這個學校的人好像完全不要緊”
-IT'S BEEN FOREVER… -LOOK AT ME…
（終於等到這天了 請看這邊）
GLOOM
（憂鬱）
What a bummer.
好憂鬱啊
My name is Nokoko Inaka.
我的名字叫井中乃來子
When I…
想到從今天起…
When I think about being back at school, my chest tightens.
就要回學校上課了，胸口就好痛苦
Nobody knows my secret… They don't know I'm a…
雖然還沒有任何人發現，但我其實…
I'm a…
我其實…
a country bumpkin!
是個鄉巴佬啊！
INAKA IS A COUNTRY GIRL.
（井中同學是鄉下人）
MISSION 29 "I'M JUST A COUNTRY GIRL."
（任務29 是鄉下小孩）
First semester was so darn tough.
第一學期真的好難熬
If my secret gets out, they'll throw rocks at me!
如果被人發現我是鄉巴佬 一定會被丟石頭的
Everyone else was having fun, but I stayed quiet by myself.
大家都在開心聊天時 只有我一個人默不作聲
Everyone made their skirts so short.
大家裙子都穿得好短
But mine was 5 cm below my knees.
只有我的裙子是膝下五公分的長度
I can't pull off a short skirt.
因為我不適合穿那麼短啊
But I'm different today!
不過今天的我不一樣！
I raised my skirt to 3 cm below my knees!
我已經把裙子改短到膝下三公分了！
It's my fall semester glow up!
這就是暑假後換新造型亮相！
I'm so embarrassed.
好害羞！
What a bummer.
好憂鬱啊
Why am I so…
為什麼我就是這麼…
That's the god of our class, Komi!
那不是我們班上的神，古見大人嗎？
Wow. Beautiful as usual.
哇，她今天也好美啊！
She's a real city girl.
那才是都會女子啊
CITY GIRL
（都會女子）
I wish I could be like Komi.
我也想像古見大人那樣
I want to be a city girl walking the business district with coffee in hand.
一手拿著星七克咖啡 走在辦公商圈的都會女子
What?
什麼？
Do classes start today?
今天要上課嗎？
I didn't buy lunch!
我沒有買午餐耶！
Seriously?
我說你啊…
Hey, Komi.
那麼古見同學
Get me a Sabowey turkey avocado sandwich.
妳去賽寶味幫我買 賽寶味火雞酪梨三明治
Honey oat, cheese, lettuce, pickles, extra olives,
加蜂蜜、燕麥、起司 生菜、酸黃瓜，黑橄欖多一點
no onions, balsamic sauce, a side of basil fries and a diet cola.
不要洋蔥，要巴薩米克黑醋醬 副餐是羅勒薯條和無糖可樂
Toasted bread, okay?
麵包要烤過喔
Go get it yourself.
你自己去買啦
Ha-ha, don't be mean, Tadano.
只野同學，你不要這麼壞心眼嘛
-S-S… -I haven't finished my homework.
-賽… -我的作業還沒寫完呢
S-Sabowey?
賽寶味？
That's another trendy city shop like Standbakes!
那不是和星七克齊名的 都會時尚名店嗎？
Wow, I want to eat a Sabowey sandwich.
真羨慕，我也好想邊吃著 賽寶味三明治…
"Compliance-wise that's no good."
“就法規而言，這樣不太好喔”
I want to try saying that!
邊這樣說！
You're my friend, aren't you?
古見同學，我們不是朋友嗎？
Help your best buddy in their hour of need!
在危急時幫幫我嘛！
NOD
（點頭）
-Yay! -You're really going?
-什麼？ -妳真的要去嗎？
Komi's going to Sabowey!
古見大人要去賽寶味！
This is a great chance!
這可是個大好機會
I'll watch her,
我要觀察她的言行舉止
and then I'll become a city girl who can eat at Sabowey too!
我也要成為一個能夠 去買賽寶味三明治的都會女子！
Hmm.
我看看…
Someone's following Komi.
有人在跟蹤古見同學
Komi, in front of such a trendy shop…
古見大人站在那個時尚空間前面
And she's standing so poised.
態度多麼光明磊落啊
I would get flustered and just go in.
換作我一定會慌慌張張地進去
-She's so calm. I love it. -TOO NERVOUS TO ENTER.
-氣定神閒，好優雅啊 -（古見同學緊張得不敢進去）
I feel like that girl's seriously mistaken.
我覺得她好像有很大的誤會
KOMI DECIDES TO GO IN.
（古見同學下定決心走進去）
I-I'll go too!
我也要進去！
FREAKED OUT BY A SHOP FULL OF COMPETENT-LOOKING PEOPLE
（幹練有才的人們所處的 時尚空間讓她嚇得要死）
Welcome!
歡迎光臨！
I can take your order here.
請到這邊點餐
It's bad to make the staff wait.
不能讓店員等太久
KOMI GOES OUT.
（古見同學總之先走了出去）
Leaving in a situation like that?!
居然在這個情況下走出去？
-What's she thinking? -GOT SCARED AND LEFT.
-她到底在想什麼啊？ -（嚇得走出去）
She's so amazing!
好帥氣啊！
Doesn't mind the staff. Keeps her own pace! Her own style!
根本不管店員 保持自我步調，重視自我風格
She just sticks to it! That's so cool!
而且貫徹到底，簡直是帥斃了！
Wow. I learned so much.
真是學到了寶貴的一課
KOMI GOES BACK IN.
（古見同學又走進來了）
ORDER
（點餐）
Hello!
歡迎光臨
Have you decided your order?
決定要點什麼了嗎？
POINT
（指）
The Sabowey Turkey Avocado?
賽寶味火雞酪梨三明治是嗎？
Take-out?
是外帶嗎？
What sort of bread?
麵包要哪一種？
Which toppings?
要哪些配料呢？
Shall I toast it?
麵包要烤嗎？
Do you want all the vegetables?
蔬菜全部夾進去可以嗎？
Which sauce?
要哪一種醬汁呢？
How about making it a lunch set?
要不要點套餐？
-PANIC -SPIN SPIN
（驚慌 腦袋一片混亂）
Komi…
古見大人…
I-If you don't have any requests,
如果沒有特別的要求
I'll make our staff recommendation.
我就幫您製作推薦口味喔
FROZEN FROM TOO MUCH INFORMATION
（其實只是因為 資訊量太大讓腦袋當機）
RECOMMENDATION
（推薦口味）
Thank you for coming!
謝謝您的惠顧！
I hope it went okay.
沒事吧？
PEEK
（探頭）
W…
好…
Wow!
好厲害！
She got her order through without speaking a word.
面對那一連串點餐詢問 居然能一語不發地點餐
Komi's powers truly know no bounds!
古見大人果真深不可測！
I… I'll be Komi's fan for life!
我要一輩子追隨她！
And someday I'll be a city girl like her!
然後總有一天要成為 像古見大人那樣的都會女子！
Alright! Now I'll try and do it like Komi.
好！我也要學古見大人那樣
I'll buy a sandwich!
來買個賽寶味三明治！
Uh, hang on…
等等…
She bought one just fine.
她成功買到了
Uh, Komi…
古見同學
This isn't…
這個買錯了
MISSION 30 "IT'S JUST A VIDEO GAME."
（任務30 是電玩遊戲）
When a person has extreme social anxiety…
所謂的“交流障礙症”
-They struggle to communicate with others. -BLOOD ALLY… BE YE FREE TO VISIT MY ABODE?
是指不擅長和人交流的一種症狀 或是指有這種症狀的人
Bear in mind…
不過需要注意的是…
BEEP
（嗶）
THUMP THUMP
（心臟狂跳）
GLANCE… SQUIRM
（偷瞥，坐立不安）
Oh!
啊！
SWIPE SWIPE
（滑手機）
…they only struggle to form connections.
這些人只是不擅長社交
It doesn't mean that they don't want to.
但並不表示他們不想和別人有往來
I WOULD BE DELIGHTED TO VISIT.
（我很樂意到妳家玩）
KOMI IS DOING HER BEST.
（古見同學鼓起幹勁）
NAKANAKA
（中中）
NAKANAKA HAS A RICH FANTASY LIFE.
（中中同學有中二病）
Well met, Princess Komilia.
歡迎妳啊，古見莉亞公主
You may enter.
進來吧
Sh-She really came!
她居然真的來了！
Th-This is my abode.
這就是我房間
INTERESTED
（覺得有趣）
Komi's here, in my room…
古見同學在我的房間裡
Wait. This is a big deal.
等等，這應該是很不得了的事吧？
The god of our class is in my room.
班上的神居然在我的房間！
I've won at life, haven't I?
這不就表示我是人生勝利組嗎？
I've gotta snap out of this and show Komi a good time.
不行，我得好好招待她才行！
K-Komi. Um…
古見同學，那個…
Sit wherever you so desire.
妳隨便坐啊
FIRST GUEST SINCE ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
（小學畢業後 第一次邀朋友來家裡）
-Tranquility! -THE STATE OF BEING TRANQUIL OR CALM.
-靜謐！ -（指安靜、平靜的狀態）
Ah yes!
對了！
I'm just getting to the best part of this game.
我現在在玩的電玩 剛好打到精彩高潮處
I'd be honored to show you.
妳一定要看看
SOME COOL IMAGE
（很酷的畫面）
Look at these graphics!
瞧瞧這遊戲介面！
These new games are so advanced.
最新遊戲現在已經進化到這地步了
It's even more beautiful than reality!
比現實更美麗的這影像如何啊？
Isn't it gorgeous?
很厲害吧？很美吧？
And the story.
還有這個故事
The worldbuilding is so complex.
這麼有深度的世界觀
The character always remains the focus!
劇情進展中不會忘了角色才是主軸
Yes! And this last scene, how can you not cry?
我懂！最後一幕是多麼催淚…
DOESN'T REALLY GET IT
（看不太懂）
Oh, hold on!
對喔
Komi's a non-gamer, an ordinary person!
古見同學是所謂的輕度玩家 也就是一般人！
She won't understand the fine points of the technology!
就算給她看最新技術 她也看不太懂！
-ONLY THINKING "NEAT." -At this rate, Komi will say…
-（只覺得“好厲害”） -糟了，這樣下去古見同學…
You bore me.
妳真是個無趣的人
…and leave!
她一定會這樣說！
I'll never get her to come over again!
然後再也不來我家玩了！
W-What can I…
我該怎麼辦？
Oh.
對了
L-Let's invite Najimi over.
我們找馴染來玩吧
The more the merrier, right?
大家一起玩比較開心
NAKANAKA BROKE CHARACTER
（中中同學的人設已完全崩壞）
You call and I appear! Da-da-dan!
一經呼喚便飛奔而來，鏘鏘鏘！
Da-dan-daaan!
鏘鏘鏘！
Terrible rhythm.
節奏亂七八糟
It's been ages since I came over.
好久沒來中中家了
Hey Komi!
嗨，古見同學
Oh, I brought Tadano too.
我還帶了只野同學來
Oh, uh, boys are not…
等一下，我不太希望男生進來…
Ah, I understand.
對喔，說得也是
It's fine.
有什麼關係嘛
You'll hardly know he's here.
只野同學沒什麼存在感
Huh?
什麼？
What do you wanna do?
玩什麼好呢？
-TADANO WAS PERMITTED TO STAY. -Let's do a four-player game.
-（只野同學獲准繼續待著） -找個可以四個人一起玩的遊戲吧
Let's play Swamp Bros!
對了，來玩《沼袋亂鬥》吧！
Why do you get to decide?
你不要擅自決定
Swamp Bros.
所謂的《沼袋亂鬥》
It's an abbreviation of Combat: Swamp Brothers.
是《沼袋明星大亂鬥》的簡稱
People love the variety of characters and dumping their opponents in a swamp to win.
把對手推進泥沼即獲勝的特殊系統 以及眾多角色登場是最大的賣點
This was huge when we were little.
我們小學的時候，這款遊戲好紅
Everyone's played it, right?
你們應該都玩過吧？
Najio!
馴吉歐！
-Who are you talking to? -Chuni!
-你在問誰啊？ -中尼！
I've tried it a couple times.
我只有稍微玩過啦
Tadashi!
只達西！
FIRST-TIMER
（從來沒玩過）
Ah, as I thought.
嗯，想也知道是那樣
Komyusho!
古米修！
Uh, guard with this…
我看看，這個按鈕是防禦…
And I think this one…
我記得這個是…
Whoopee!
衝啊！
The combat has begun!
大亂鬥已經開始了！
Komi!
古見同學！
You're a sitting duck! Yoooo!
妳就是絕佳目標啊！
-Oh! -I won't let you touch my ally.
-什麼？ -絕不讓你欺負我的盟友！
Nicely done.
挺有兩下子的嘛
This button is how you move.
然後這個是移動按鈕
Come at me!
很好！
Yes! Like that!
沒錯，就是這樣！
And here's how you jump…
然後這個是跳躍…
Komi!
古見同學！
Keep hitting the jump button.
快連按跳躍按鈕
The jump button!
跳躍按鈕！
I invited her to my castle.
既然邀請她來我的城堡
I've got to make sure Komi has a good time!
我一定要讓古見同學盡興而歸！
I won't let her get smashed!
絕不讓你把她變成攻擊的目標！
Not so fast!
妳太天真了！
You haven't changed one bit!
和小學的時候沒什麼兩樣！
-Combo and attack! -No!
-連續技中一瞬間的空檔！ -慘了！
Heh. I'm still a rank above you.
呵呵，看來我還是比妳強
Now for the finishing bl…
讓我給妳最後一擊…
Ah.
嗚
I'll admit you once were better than me.
小學的時候你的確比我強
But.
但是…
I've got someone to protect now.
現在我有值得守護的事物
"Lose" isn't in my dictionary!
我的字典裡沒有“輸掉”這兩個字！
This game doesn't reward people for simply wanting to win!
別以為靠鬥志就能贏 這個遊戲沒那麼簡單！
Oh, if you fall in the swamp, the mud slows you down.
對了，掉到泥沼裡後 身上沾了泥巴，動作會變遲緩
Press the R2--
要按R2按鈕…
I'M SORRY…
（對不起…）
Oh, that's part of the game. Don't worry about it.
本來就是這樣的遊戲，不要緊
Right here.
按這裡
Yes! You've got it!
沒錯，就是這樣！
What?!
什麼？
The Mud Cancel?!
泥巴特殊攻擊？
Who pulled off this advanced technique?
是誰用了這麼高等的招式？
Where are you looking?
你在看哪裡？
No!
糟了！
W-Wow! I beat Najimi!
耶，我贏了！我打敗馴染了！
I lost!
我輸了
Did you see that? My first victory!
看到了嗎？我第一次打敗你呢！
No! That was a fluke!
不算！剛才只是僥倖罷了！
Huh?
什麼？
I was just caught off guard by Komi's mud attack!
我只是不小心 被古見同學的泥巴打到了！
Don't be a sore loser!
死不認輸很難看耶！
Next time I'll bring my A game!
那接下來我要認真打！
Fine.
可以啊
I'm finished getting warmed-up anyway.
我剛好也暖身完畢了
MISSION 31 "IT'S JUST A PART-TIME JOB."
（任務31 去打工）
BEEP
（嗶）
H…!
你…
Sorry to call you on your day off.
假日還找妳幫忙，真是不好意思！
The other person suddenly had to cancel.
原本要一起打工的人臨時不能來
I asked around, but nobody had time.
雖然到處問過，但大家都沒空
Let's get started!
那就開始吧！
A job handing out tissues!
打工發面紙！
COULDN'T REFUSE
（拒絕不了別人的請託）
I have to hand out 5,000 today.
今天得發完五千包才行
It's just handing out tissues. Komi, you'll be fine.
不過只是發面紙 古見同學應該也做得來吧？
I'll be working over there. Thanks, guys!
那我去那邊發，這邊就拜託你們了！
Here!
請拿！
Please take one!
請拿一份！
Here you go! Hey! Tissues! Anyone need tissues?
請拿！是面紙喔！需要面紙嗎？
FIRED UP
（鼓起幹勁）
Hey, that girl's so pretty!
快看，那個女孩好美啊！
For sure. What's she doing?
真的耶，她在做什麼呀？
-Handing out tissues? -Let's go get some!
-在發面紙嗎？ -我們去跟她拿！
But she's not handing them out.
可是她好像沒有在發耶
Then what's she doing?
那她是在幹什麼？
Maybe we shouldn't get involved.
或許不該跟她說話？
RE-FIRED UP!
（再度鼓起幹勁！）
ABOUT TO CRY
（快哭了）
FIRED UP!
（鼓起幹勁！）
128 MENTAL DAMAGE (22 LEFT)
（古見同學的心靈遭到128點的傷害 殘餘22點）
Huh? Was she handing out tissues?
等等，剛才她是要發面紙給我嗎？
I should have taken some.
應該收下才對
Oh no! Right now…
慘了！我現在…
-I really want some tissues! -WOMAN WHO REALLY WANTS TISSUES.
-非常需要面紙！ -（急需面紙的人）
I feel like I might sneeze.
鼻子好癢，好想打噴嚏
I spilled my cola. My hands are sticky.
剛才喝的可樂灑出來 弄得手黏答答的
I'm going to see someone, but I'm sweaty.
約了人等下見面，現在卻滿頭大汗
I've got gum stuck to my shoe.
鞋底還黏著剛才踩到的口香糖
And I forgot my handkerchief!
偏偏這種時候又忘了帶手帕！
-WOMAN WHO REALLY WANTS TISSUES. -So I really need some tissues!
-所以我非常需要面紙！ -（急需面紙的人）
Oh! Over there, could she be…
啊，那個人莫非在…
Handing out tissues?
她在發面紙嗎？
But it'd be weird if I asked for some.
可是主動去索取，感覺好貪心
The beautiful tissue girl is looking my way.
發面紙的美少女正在看向我這邊
Will you give me some tissues?
她要給我嗎？她要給我面紙嗎？
Tissues… I want some tissues…
面紙…我想要面紙…
-KOMI VISION. -Tissues…
-（在古見同學眼中看起來是這樣） -面紙…
Thank you!
謝謝妳！
SHE CLEARLY WANTED TISSUES SO KOMI MANAGED TO OBLIGE.
（但對方明顯很想要面紙 古見同學還是鼓起勇氣拿給了她）
Oh, you really are handing out tissues!
果然是在發面紙對吧？
Can I have some?
可以給我們一包嗎？
I'll take a pack!
請給我一包面紙！
Me too!
我也要！
Alright!
請注意！
-Line up for tissues! -YAMAI APPEARED OUT NOWHERE.
-想領取面紙的人請排隊！ -（不知從哪裡冒出來的山井同學）
The maximum is five packets per person!
每人最多只能領取五包！
EMPTY
（空空如也）
We did it!
發完了耶！
That's amazing Komi! Thank you!
古見同學真是太厲害了，謝謝妳！
I'll give you a third of the money!
打工的酬勞我會分成三等份！
Alright, see ya!
那麼辛苦了！
A THIRD?
（三等份？）
So… hot…
好熱！
Good morning!
早安！
MISSION 32 "IT'S JUST… SOMETHING ON YOUR FACE."
（任務32 臉上沾到東西了）
Good morning, Komi.
早安，古見同學
You're early today.
今天妳來得好早
Huh? What's wrong?
嗯？怎麼了嗎？
Komi?
古見同學？
CAN'T DECIDE IF SHE SHOULD SAY SOMETHING.
（古見同學在猶豫 不知道該不該提醒他）
KOMI DECIDES TO JUST OBSERVE FOR NOW.
（古見同學決定先觀察看看 沾到的究竟是什麼）
CAN'T FIGURE OUT WHAT IT IS.
（仔細看還是看不出那是什麼）
OKAY!!
（下定決心！）
POINT
（指）
What is it?
什麼事啊？
-ARE YOU TADANO? (HE'S USUALLY PERCEPTIVE) -What's that mean?
-（是只野同學？洞察力明明很強） -什麼意思啊？
WHY NOT TELL HIM WITH A NOTE?
（可以寫在筆記本上告訴他！）
BUT HE MIGHT FEEL HURT…
（但萬一傷了他的自尊…）
JUST DON'T MENTION IT?
（那不要告訴他比較好？）
HE'LL BE MORE HURT IF PEOPLE SEE.
（但被大家看到不是會更受傷嗎？）
Komi?
古見同學？
GETS CONFUSED AND STARTS CRYING
（腦中一片混亂，快哭了）
Hey Komi! Tadano!
嗨，古見喵，只野喵！
I'M SAV…
（救星來了！）
Hello!
早安，哈囉！
What's up today, Komi?
妳從剛才就怪怪的 怎麼了？古見同學
What are you doing, Komi?
古見同學，妳在幹什麼呀？
Good morning!
早安！
N-N-Nice weather today!
今天天氣也很好呢！
Good morning Komi!
早安，古見同學！
Loving you as usual!
今天我也很愛妳喔！
Komi got here before me again!
古見同學又比我早來！
Your forbidden power is blazing as usual.
今天禁忌的力量仍舊十分燦爛！
GASP
（起身）
It was a dream.
原來是一場夢
THE NEXT DAY
（隔天）
Good morning!
早安！
Good morning, Komi.
早安，古見同學
You're early today.
今天妳來得好早
Najimi, you skipped out on the meeting again yesterday.
馴染，你昨天又沒來開會了吧？
What gives, Tadano?
怎樣？只野同學
You want to hang out with me that badly?
你就這麼想和我在一起嗎？
Najimi, about the papers for the culture festival…
馴染，關於文化祭的資料…
Najimi, that book I lent you…
馴染，我上次借你的書…
Najimi, you…
馴染，你啊…
Najimi!
馴染！
Naji…
馴…
Huh?
喔？
What's wrong, Komi?
怎麼了？古見同學
SQUIRM
（扭捏）
CALL ME BY MY NAME TOO.
（請你也直接叫我的名字）
Huh? Your name?
什麼？名字？
What do you…
什麼意思啊？
"You and Najimi are friends,
“只野同學和馴染是朋友
so you say, 'Najimi' right?"
所以你都叫他‘馴染’對吧？”
Oh, yes.
啊，是的
…SO,
（…所以）
Yes.
怎麼了？
CALL ME "SHOKO" TOO.
（也請你叫我“硝子”）
BOOM
（臉紅）
No, no it's just like, you know!
不行啦，這樣太超過了！
Calling a girl by her name…
怎麼可以直接叫女孩子的名字呢…
Hey Tadano!
嗨，只野同學！
Are you trying to say I'm not a girl?
你的意思是說我就不是個女孩子嗎？
You can zip it.
你給我閉嘴
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO, IT'S OKAY.
（如果你不想叫也沒關係）
I-It's not that I…
我不是不想叫啦！
I just… how can I put it?
那個，該怎麼說呢？
Shoko.
硝子
-SHOKO… -JOLT
（硝子… 戰慄）
FEELS WEIRD, BUT NOT IN A BAD WAY.
（是很奇妙的感覺，但不覺得討厭）
Now you try it, Tadano!
好了，只野同學也說說看嘛！
Shoko! It's Shoko!
硝子！叫她硝子！
Stop.
你住口
Do I really have to say it?
不這樣叫不行嗎？
I'M NOT TRYING TO FORCE YOU.
（其實也不用那麼勉強）
Of course you have to!
當然不行啊！
It's a request from Komi herself!
這可是古見同學衷心的請求耶！
Sho…
硝…
HE COULDN'T SAY IT.
（他說不出口）
Komi.
古見同學
-He couldn't say it. -You got no balls!
-他說不出口 -你這個窩囊廢，太不爭氣了！
CALL ME "SHOKO" TOO.
（也請你叫我“硝子”）
Okay, next!
好，那接下來
Komi, now you try.
換古見同學說說看！
Hey. You're going to put Komi through this too?
喂，這套酷刑 你也要讓古見同學體驗啊？
Of course!
那是當然的啊
She's the one who brought it up.
既然希望別人叫自己的名字
She should start it, right?
那就該從自己做起不是嗎？
Flawless logic!
太有道理了！
Alright, try saying it!
那就來叫叫看吧！
By the way, Tadano's name is Hitohito.
順便跟妳說 只野同學的名字叫“仁人”
Just in case you forgot.
怕妳不記得，提醒妳一下
I should hope she remembers…
希望她有記住
No writing it down either.
不可以寫在紙上
HITOHITO
（仁人同學）
Hi…
仁…
Komi couldn't say it either.
古見同學也說不出口
CAN WE JUST GO BACK TO HOW IT WAS?
（還是照平常那樣叫就好了）
You guys are hopeless.
你們倆真是的
Well, Hitohito is tough. Doesn't roll off the tongue.
不過“仁人”這個名字 本來就不好唸，非常不順口
Oh, Tadano. You've had a sesame seed on your face all day.
對了，只野同學 從早上你臉上一直黏了一顆芝麻
You have a sesame seed on your face.
我說你臉上有芝麻
Najimi could say it all.
這些馴染都說出口了
Subtitle translation by: Claire Tanaka
字幕翻譯：馬慈光